Lloyd: So now that you've
completed session 2, it's time
to complete the relevant section
in the assessment booklet.
So if you open your assessment
booklet and scroll down to section
two, and this is Understand Key
Principles When Writing Code.
As you will know this is meeting
learning outcome three: understand
key principles when writing code.
So just to be aware that it is learning
outcome three, not learning outcome two,
that you're covering in this session.
One of the things that is being
provided for you in the assessment
is an example of JavaScript code.
So this is taken from the course
materials, and it'll help you with
your answers to question one  to four.
So you can utilise this, it's exactly
the same as in the course materials, and
they'll just help you with your answers.
So for question one, you can look at the
above JavaScript example and explain how
the variables have been used and define
what an operand on an operation is.
So how have the variables
been used within the code?
So if you can look at that, so you
need to explain how those variables
have been used and then what is an
operand, and what is an operation?
So what do they do?
What do they carry out?
What function do they have?
Then for question two, it's asking you:
using the above JavaScript example,
describe the principles of functions.
So again, if you look up at the example
code, what functions have been useful?
So what is the purpose of
the functions in there?
And for question three, again,
using the JavaScript example,
what is meant by iterations?
So looking at that, you learned about the
iterations within the course materials, so
how have they been used within that code?
What is the purpose of
iterations within that code?
And for the final question there, it is
asking you to use the JavaScript example,
explain what was meant by control flow.
So again, how has control flow
been used within this example?
So use your learning from the course
materials and your understanding
of the different components make
up a section of script, explain
what is meant by control flow.
For question five, it's asking
you to explain the use of
queues, stacks, and lists.
So this isn't relating to the example,
this is a question on its own.
So, using your learning from
the course materials, why do you
use queues, stacks and lists?
Why are they useful?
What is their purpose?
And for question six, it's
asking you to explain what is
meant by the term collection.
So what do we mean when we're talking
about a collection in terms of coding?
And then for question seven, we've
also had a look at some Python code
from the course materials, which
will help you answer question seven,
and using the above python example,
define what is meant by recursion.
So how are recursions used
within that piece of code?
What is the purpose of recursions?
What do they do?
So once you've done that, if you
check through all of your answers,
carry out a spelling and grammar
check, proofread everything to
make sure you're happy with it.
And then save that and you
can move on to session three.